{
    "id": "e80326eae35443a09ee5025605f3dd85",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to go now. Here now is an ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "preposition",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing there? Here there is a/an ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "conjunction",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He left ten minutes ago. Here ten is a/an ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a mistake in line  Here in is a/an ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Masons build houses. Here build is a/an ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Though she was unwell, she went to work. Here though is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been reading since morning. Here morning is a/an .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "noun",
                "pronoun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He died two years ago. Here ago is a/an .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "As she was late, we went without her. Here as is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The Nile is the longest river in the world. Here Nile is a/an .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened to you? Here you is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My family live in different parts of India. Here different is a/an .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}